Finding Aid for School of Natural Resources and Environment (University of Michigan) Records 1903-2012.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Topical Files, 1967-1990; 11.5 linear feet
  - 1977-1990
    - Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program, 1985-1987 (Box 28)
    - Egypt Collaboration, 1985 (Box 28)
    - Endangered Species Studies, 1978; 1981; 1985 (Box 28)
    - Endangered Species Technical Bulletin, 1983-1988 (Box 28)
    - Energy
      - General, 1982-1985 (Box 28)
      - Energy Cost Avoidance Project, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Environmental Advocacy Film-Lecture Series, 1987-1989 (Box 28)
    - Environmental Law Society (UM), 1986-1988 (Box 28)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
    - Environmental Science Proposal, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Equipment Proposal Meetings, 1982 (Box 28)
    - Executive Committee
      - General, 1983/84-1986/87; 4 folders (Box 28)
      - Affirmative Action, 1987 (Box 28)
      - Elections, 1988-1990 (Box 28)
      - Strategic Planning, 1986-1988 (Box 28)
    - Extension Service, 1982-1984 (Box 28)
    - Faculty
      - General, 1964; 1972; 1979-1989 (Box 28)
      - Academic Affiliations, Survey of, 1985 (Box 28)
      - Faculty Needs, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Faculty Retreat, May 1987 (Box 28)
      - Faculty Workday (retreat), December 1983 (Box 28)
      - Faculty Workshop, January 1988 (Box 28)
      - Minority Faculty Appointments, 1988-1989 (Box 53)
      - Teaching Loads
        - General, 1976; 1984-1989 (Box 28)
        - Faculty Surveys, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Federated Garden Club Scholarships (Box 29)
      - General, 1984 (Box 29)
      - Student Applications, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Field Studies (includes Camp Filibert Roth), 1983-1988 (Box 29)
    - Financial Aid, 1984-1990 (Box 29)
    - Fish Consumption Study, 1985-1990 (Box 29)
    - Fisheries Research, Institute for, 1986 (Box 29)
    - Fishery Science, 1983-1985; 1988 (Box 29)
    - Forestry
      - General, 1982-1990 (Box 29)
      - Cooperative State Research Service Review, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Geographic Information Systems, 1983-1989 (Box 29)
    - Glenmeade Trust Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
    - Global Change, 1989-1990 (Box 29)
    - Global Involvement, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1983 (Box 29)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 1984-1985 (Box 29)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center (GLMWC)
      - General, 1982-1988; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Associate Director Search, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Great Lakes Conflict, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1987; 1989 (Box 29)
    - International Programs, 1985-1990 (Box 29)
    - International Research, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
    - International Resource Management, 1986 (Box 29)
    - International Seminars
      - General, 1985-1986 (Box 29)
      - Forestry
        - General
          - 1983-1985 (Box 29)
          - 1986-1990 (Box 29)
        - Director Search, 1989 (Box 53)
      - Parks
        - General
          - 1980, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 29)
          - 1985 (Box 29)
          - 1986 (Box 29)
          - 1987-1988 (Box 30)
        - Director Search, 1984 (Box 53)
      - Watershed Research, 1985 (Box 30)
    - International Students, 1986 (Box 30)
    - International Studies Advisory Council (UM), 1989-1990 (Box 30)
    - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources, 1984-1987 (Box 30)
    - Joint Programs and Interunit Initiatives, 1987; 1990 (Box 30)
    - Key Relationships (SNR development issues), 1985 (Box 30)
    - King/Chavez/Parks Visiting Scholars, 1988-1990 (Box 30)
    - Lab Fees, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Landscape Architecture Program
      - General, 1982-1988 (Box 30)
      - American Society of Landscape Architecture, 1984; 1988 (Box 30)
    - Lectures
      - General, 1985-1988 (Box 30)
      - Laird, Norton Distinguished Speaker Series, 1983-1986 (Box 30)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, 1987-1989 (Box 30)
    - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of, 1984-1990 (Box 30)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Marygrove College, 1986 (Box 30)
    - Masters Program
      - General, 1983-1989 (Box 30)
      - Orientation Materials, 1986/87 (Box 30)
    - Masters Projects
      - General, 1984-1990; 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Faculty Workshop, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Meeman Archive, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Mentoring Program, 1987-1989 (Box 30)
    - Michigan, State of
      - General, 1985-1990 (Box 30)
      - Department of Natural Resources, 1983-1990 (Box 30)
      - Department of Public Health's Council on Environmental Quality, 1985-1990 (Box 30)
    - Michigan Atmospheric Deposition Laboratory (MADLAB), 1987 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Consolidated Gas Company, 1987-1988 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Forestry Association, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Media, 1982; 1987-1988 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Sea Grant College Program, 1981-1990; 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Michigan State University / Michigan Technological University / University of Michigan Collaboration, 1977; 1985-1990 (Box 31)
      (includes atmospheric deposition research)
    - Michigan Toxic Dumpsite Conference, 1983 (Box 31)
    - Minority Internship Program, 1988-1990 (Box 31)
    - National Association of Professional Forestry Schools and Colleges, 1985-1990 (Box 31)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1987 (Box 31)
    - National Park Service (see also International Seminars--Parks)
      - General, 1982-1983 (Box 31)
      - Proposal for a Cooperative Park Study Unit, 1988 (Box 31)
    - National Science Foundation, 1990 (Box 31)
    - National Wildlife Federation, Great Lakes Natural Resource Center
      - General, 1981-1990 (Box 31)
      - Scientist Search, 1985-1990 (Box 53)
    - Natural Resources Club (SNR), 1983-1984 (Box 31)
    - Natural Resources Economics Program
      - General, 1978; 1981-1988 (Box 31)
      - Faculty Search, 1987-1988 (Box 53)
    - Natural Science Library, 1987-1989 (Box 31)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies (OTS), 1983-1990 (Box 31)
    - Organizational Charts (SNR), 1982-1985 (Box 31)
    - Peace Corps, 1985-1986 (Box 31)
    - Peer Institutions, 1983; 1987 (Box 31)
    - Ph.D. Program, 1983-1987 (Box 31)
    - Plant Operations, 1984 (Box 31)
    - The Population-Environment Dynamics Project, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Post-Doctoral Scholars (Box 32)
      - General, 1983-1987 (Box 32)
      - Recruitment, 1987 (Box 53)
    - President, Office of, 1986-1988 (Box 32)
    - President's Reports, 1980-1987 (Box 32)
    - Presidential Initiatives Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
    - Presidential Search Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 53)
    - Properties (SNR), 1983 (Box 32)
    - Publications and Communication Activities, 1980-1985 (Box 32)
    - Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 1982-1989 (Box 32)
    - Rain Forest Action Movement, 1988-1989 (Box 32)
    - Recruitment (of students), 1983-1988; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Recycling, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Regents, 1984-1985 (Box 32)
    - Regents Fellowships, 1983; 1989 (Box 32)
    - Remote Sensing, 1982-1988 (Box 32)
    - Research
      - General, 1982-1990 (Box 32)
      - Faculty Research Interests, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Research Assistants, 1983-1985 (Box 32)
    - Research Committee
      - General, 1984-1990 (Box 32)
      - Report: International Research in SNR, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Research Incentive Program, 1988-1989 (Box 32)
    - Research Seminar, 1986; 1989 (Box 32)
    - Resource Institutions and Human Behavior Specialization, 1983-1984 (Box 32)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1982-1985 (Box 32)
    - Society of American Foresters
      - General, 1972; 1978-1989 (Box 32)
      - Accreditation
        - General
          - 1973, 1982-1984 (Box 32)
          - 1985-1990 (Box 32)
        - Reports (Box 33)
          - Interim Status Report for Continuation of Accreditation, 1988 (Box 33)
          - Self-Evaluation Report, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Specialization Coordinators, 1984-1988; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Speeches (Crowfoot), 1987; 1989 (Box 33)
    - Staff Advisory Committee
      - 1983-1984 (Box 33)
      - 1985-1986, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Staff Advisory Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 33)
    - Staff Retreats, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Students
      - General, 1984; 1987-1989 (Box 33)
      - Graduate Recruitment, 1985-1986 (Box 33)
      - Minority Students and Recruitment, 1981-1987 (Box 33)
      - Ph.D. Students
        - General, 1986-1990 (Box 33)
        - Orientation Materials, 1986 (Box 33)
        - Statement of Purpose, 1986 (Box 53)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2016 ]
      - Placement of Grad Students, undated (Box 33)
      - Student Planning Assistance to Community Environments (SPACE), 1979; 1983 (Box 33)
      - Student Policy Advisory Committee (SPAC), 1981-1988 (Box 33)
      - Teaching Assistants, 1982-1986 (Box 33)
      - Undergraduate Recruitment, 1983; 1986-1989 (Box 33)
    - Task Forces
      - General, 1983-1984 (Box 33)
      - Academic Services Task Force Final Report, 1984 (Box 33)
      - Integrative Studies and Core Courses Task Force (ISCCTF) Final Report, 1983 (Box 33)
      - Management Specialization, Report, 1984 (Box 33)
      - Temporary Specialization Task Forces, 1983 (Box 33)
      - Usage of Microprocessors, Task Force on, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Theses and Practicums, 1986; 1989 (Box 33)
    - Undergraduate Initiatives Fund Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1985-1989 (Box 33)
    - Urban, Technological, and Environmental Planning Program (UTEP), 1982-1989; undated (Box 33)
    - Vice Presidents
      - Academic Affairs, 1982-1988; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Government Relations, 1984-1987 (Box 33)
      - Research, 1984-1989 (Box 33)
    - Vice Provost for Information Technology, 1988 (Box 34)
    - Visitors
      - General, 1984-1990 (Box 34)
      - Bingham, Gail, 1987 (Box 34)
      - Cardenal, Lorenzo, 1986 (Box 34)
      - Fox, Matthew, 1990 (Box 34)
      - Myers, Norman, 1989 (Box 34)
      - Reilly, William, 1990 (Box 34)
      - Tarak, Arturo, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Warm Water Lab, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Water Resources Research, 1984-1990 (Box 34)
    - Whittemore, Harlow, Lectureship, 1977-1978 (Box 34)
    - Wilderness Society, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Wildland Management Center
      - General, 1979-1988; undated; 4 folders (Box 34)
      - Review
        - General, 1986-1987 (Box 34)
        - Report to the Review Committee, 1986 (Box 34)
        - Review Committee Report, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Wildlife Specialization, 1984-1987 (Box 34)
    - World Hunger Education-Action Committee (whe-ac), 1986 (Box 34)
    - Yale University, 1983-1987 (Box 34)
    - Zimbabwe Program, 1989-1990 (Box 34)
    - Zimbabwe Project, 1989-1990 (Box 34)
- Associate Dean's Correspondence Files, 1983-1989
  The Associate Dean's Correspondence Files series (3 linear ft.) consists of outgoing correspondence of Associate Dean John Bassett arranged chronologically. Topics generally relate to academic and curricular issues and cover the years 1983/84 through 1989.
  - 1983/84-1985 September, 7 volumes (Box 39)
  - October 1985-January 1986 (Box 40)
  - May 1986-August 1987, 5 volumes (Box 40)
  - September 1987-August 1988, 4 volumes (Box 41)
  - January 1989-October 1989, 2 volumes (Box 41)
- Stewart Marquis Files, 1980s
  The series of Stewart Marquis Files (2 linear ft.) from the 1980s documents course development and curricular activities of Stewart Marquis, former Professor of Resource Policy and Regional Planning (1968-1986). The majority of the papers are handwritten notes and are generally grouped by course.
  - Course Files (Box 42)
  - Course Files (Box 43)
    (continued)
- Reports
  The Reports series (.5 linear ft.) consists of reports generated by SNR for various purposes, including self-evaluations of academic programs for reaccreditation, workshop proceedings, and overview papers on SNR's progress in a given area, such as international research.
  - Behavior and Environment Program
    - Self Evaluation Report, 1981 (Box 44)
    - Site Visit Report, 1981 (Box 44)
  - "Forestry Resources Program, Reaccreditation Report," (to Society of American Foresters), 1979 (Box 44)
  - "International Research in SNR,", 1988 (Box 44)
  - "Progress Report on the Study of Natural Resource and Environmental Conflict,", 1982 (Box 44)
  - "A Profile and Sense of Direction of the SNR,", June 1974 (Box 44)
  - "A Process for the Michigan Department of Natural Resources to Build Consensus on Intensive Forestry Practices in Michigan,", 1984 (Box 44)
  - "Recruitment Strategy,", 1984 (Box 44)
  - "Report on the 1987 International Seminar on Forest Administration and Management," 1987 (Box 44)
  - Research Priorities in Conservation Biology Workshop Proceedings, 1987 (Box 44)
  - "SNR: Status and Direction for the Future; A Background Report,", 1981 (Box 44)
  - "Self-Evaluation Report for Reaccreditation by the Society of American Foresters,", circa 1970s (Box 44)
  - "Self-Evaluation Report for Society of American Foresters Accreditation,", 1984 (Box 44)
  - "Water Management in Michigan: Task E,", 1985 (Box 44)
- Scrapbooks (of Newspaper Clippings)
  The Scrapbooks series consists of two scrapbooks of news clippings in one box covering the years from 1927 to 1942 and titled, "Items of Interest Concerning the School of Forestry and Conservation, and Forestry."
  - "Items of interest concerning the School of Forestry and Conservation, and Forestry from, 1927-August 1935 (Box 48)
  - "Items of interest concerning the School of Forestry and Conservation, and Forestry from to June 30, 1942", September 1935 (Box 48)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series is comprised of two subseries: Photographs and Glass Slides of Michigan. The Photographs subseries includes one linear foot of photographs, an outsize folder, and one photograph album. All photographs are black and white and range in dates from 1904 to 1964. The photographs are separated into the categories School of Natural Resources, Michigan, and Other States. SNR subjects include faculty, student class photographs, and Forestry Club activities and group photos. As the student Forestry Club seems to have been a general club for all SNR students, for years which a class photograph does not exist the researcher is advised to examine the Forestry Club photos. The photographs of Michigan are arranged alphabetically by subject and consist mostly of scenes of wooded areas, logging activities, and lumber companies. In addition, there are two photos of Rock Harbor Lighthouse. The group of photographs from Other States are also arranged alphabetically by subject, which include fire fighters, forest fires, forest rangers, and logging and lumber companies. Additional photographs and negatives received in the 1995 accession are housed here and are described in the inventory.
  The four small boxes of Glass Slides of Michigan (1 linear foot) are divided into three geographic regions: Upper Peninsula, Northern Lower Michigan, and Southern Lower Michigan. Dates are provided in the box list where available and seem to range from roughly 1910 to 1940. Subjects with the most slides include Isle Royale (1936 fire), Pictured Rocks, Belle Isle, Clinton River, Cranbrook Institute, Woodlawn Cemetery, Hartland, various Ann Arbor scenes, Huron River, and a number of Michigan state parks.
  - Photographs
    - School of Natural Resources
      - Alumni, 1923; 1 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Banquets
        - Annual Banquets, 1904; 1908; 2 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Banquet in Honor of Gifford Pinchot, 1909; 1 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Faculty
        (1 black and white image each except where indicated)
        - Arnold, Keith, undated (Box 49)
        - Baxter, Dow V., undated; 1 images black and white; 2 negatives (Box 49)
        - Beeton, Alfred M., undated (Box 49)
        - Cain, Stanley A., undated (Box 49)
        - Demmon, Elwood R., undated (Box 49)
        - Fontanna, Stanley G., undated (Box 49)
        - Johnson, Carl, undated (Box 49)
        - Johnson, William, undated (Box 49)
        - Kauffman, C.H. (bas relief of), 1930; 2 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Leonard, Justin W., undated (Box 49)
        - McFadden, James, undated (Box 49)
        - Matthews, Donald M., undated (Box 49)
        - Roth, Filibert, undated; 2 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Spalding, Volney Morgan, 1918 (Box 49)
        - Spurr, Stephen H., undated; 3 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Young, Leigh J., undated (Box 49)
      - Silvics Laboratory, 1927; 1 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Stinchfield Woods, 1932 undated; 13 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Students
        - General, undated; 2 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Class Photographs
          - 1904, 1905; 1906; 1907 (Box 49)
          - 1910-1913 (Folder 1)
            (call no. UBImum/C241)
          - 1914 (Folder 1)
            (Postgraduate Class)
          - 1915 (Box 49)
          - 1916 (Box 49)
          - 1917 (Folder 1)
          - Unidentified Classes (2 black and white images, possibly classes of and 1909), 1908 (Box 49)
        - Forestry Club
          - 1910-1919 (Volume 1)
          - 1930, 1931 (Folder 1)
          - Excerpts from an album (includes Eberwhite Woods photos), 1936 (Box 49)
          - 1936, 1937; 1938; 1939; 1942; 1945 (Folder 1)
          - 1948/49, 1950/51; undated (Box 49)
        - Saginaw Forest (Field Day), 1918-1919 (Box 49)
    - Michigan
      - Au Sable Forest Farm, undated; 4 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Blaney Park, undated; 11 images black and white (Box 49)
      - David Ward Estate, 1908 undated; 50 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Huron National Forest, undated; 2 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Lake States Forest Experiment Station, undated; 4 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Logging and Lumber Companies
        - Benzie Co. and Betsie River, undated; 10 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Cadillac (mostly Cobbs and Mitchell Inc.), 1911; 1920-1921; undated; 17 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Grand Traverse County, undated; 16 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Johannesburg (North Mill and Johannesburg Sawmill), undated; 25 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Leelanau County, undated; 4 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Loud Lumber Co. (Charles, MI), 1914-1915; 5 images black and white (Box 49)
        - W.J. Brinen's Photos of W.J. Brinen Lumber Co., Thayer Lumber Co., and L.G. Mason Lumber Co., 1938-1941; 31 images black and white
          copies of older images
        - Miscellaneous (Box 49)
      - Rock Harbor Lighthouse, undated; 2 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Tindal and Jackson Estate, undated; 5 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Miscellaneous and unidentified (Box 49)
    - Other States (than Michigan)
      - Firefighters (includes camp scenes), undated; 11 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Forest Fires and Related Activities (includes fire trains), 1926; 1929 undated; 30 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Forest Rangers
        - Fishery Management, 1911 undated; 5 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Lookout Stations (interiors and exteriors), undated; 11 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Reforestation Activities, 1914 undated; 28 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Research and Forest Activities, undated; 18 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Logging and Lumber Companies
        - Alabama and Arkansas (primarily Dierks Lumber and Coal Company), 1926 undated; 18 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Arizona (primarily Saginaw and Manistee Lumber Company), undated; 6 images black and white (Box 49)
        - California, undated; 8 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Georgia, undated; 12 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Idaho, 1910 undated; 7 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Louisiana, undated; 9 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Mississippi, 1920 undated; 8 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Montana, 1905-1914; undated; 20 images black and white (Box 49)
        - New York, 1919 undated; 8 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Oklahoma, Oregon, undated; 25 images black and white (Box 49)
        - South Carolina, 1946 undated; 3 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Washington, 1915; 1918 undated; 20 images black and white (Box 49)
          (see also Nevue, Wilfred)
        - Miscellaneous States and Unidentified, 34 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Machinery, undated; 25 images black and white (Box 49)
      - Nevue, Wilfred, Collection of Lumber Photos
        - Akley, Minnesota, 1905-1906; 11 images black and white (Box 49)
        - Washington
          - Aberdeen, 1907 undated; 3 images black and white (Box 49)
          - Buckley, 1900-1908; undated; 7 images black and white (Folder 1)
          - Grotto, undated (Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Subjects (Box 49)
  - Negatives
    - 1964 undated (Box 49)
    - 100th Anniversary (Box 71)
    - Faculty
      - Brewer, Garry D., undated (Box 71)
      - Crowfoot, James, undated (Box 71)
      - Stapp, William, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Photographs - Faculty
    - Faculty
      - Spalding, Volney Morgan, undated (Folder BImu/C241)
      - Population Study (Karl F. Lagler and Gerald P. Cooper), 1954 (Folder BImu/C241)
      - Roth, Filibert, 1914 (Folder BImu/C241)
    - Forestry Club
      - 1924 (Folder BImu/C241)
      - 1929 (Folder BImu/C241)
      - 1933 (Folder BImu/C241)
      - 1941 (Folder BImu/C241)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1931; undated; 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Photographs, 1904-2003
    - School of Natural Resources
      - Biological Station
        - 1993 (Box 70)
        - 1999, 7 folders (Box 70)
      - Camp Hayo-Went-Ha, circa, 1998 (Box 70)
        (includes negatives)
      - Commencement
        - 1999 (Box 70)
        - 2000 (Box 70)
        - 2002 (Box 70)
        - 2003 (Box 70)
      - Dana Building Renovation, 1998 (Box 70)
      - Faculty
        - Faculty Photograph, 1950s (Box 70)
        - First Four Deans, circa 1974; 1 folders; 1 oversize photographs located in box 76 (Box 70)
          (Seated l-r: Stanley G. Fontana and Samuel T. Dana, Standing l-r: Keith Arnold and Stephen Spurr)
        - Allan, David, undated (Box 70)
        - Anderson, Eddie, undated (Box 70)
        - Andrews, Horace J., undated (Box 70)
        - Andrews, Richard N.L., undated (Box 70)
        - Arnold, Keith, undated; 1 folders; 1 oversize photographs located in box 76 (Box 70)
        - Bardach, John E., undated (Box 70)
        - Bartman, Edward, 1988 (Box 70)
        - Bassett, John, undated (Box 70)
        - Baxter, Dow V., undated (Box 70)
        - Beeton, Alfred, undated (Box 70)
        - Bell, David A., undated (Box 70)
        - Belovsky, Gary E., undated (Box 70)
        - Bender, Maurice, undated (Box 70)
        - Bergsma, Ralph, 1964 (Box 70)
        - Bierbaum, Rosina, 2002; 2006; undated (Box 70)
        - Bourne, Godfrey, undated (Box 70)
        - Boyle, James, undated (Box 70)
        - Brabec, Elizabeth, undated (Box 70)
        - Brewer, Garry D., undated (Box 70)
        - Brinser, Ayers, undated (Box 70)
        - Brown, Donald, undated (Box 70)
        - Brown, Terry J., 1998; undated (Box 70)
        - Bruneau, Glenn, undated (Box 70)
        - Bryant, Bunyan, undated (Box 70)
        - Bulkley, Jonathan, undated (Box 70)
        - Burch, John, undated (Box 70)
        - Burchfield, James, undated (Box 70)
        - Burgess, Jan, undated (Box 70)
        - Cares, Charles, 1959; undated (Box 70)
        - Carow, John, 1978; 1 folders; 1 oversize photographs located in box 76 (Box 70)
        - Chambers, Walter, undated (Box 70)
        - Chase, Warren W., undated (Box 70)
        - Cowan, Archibald B., undated (Box 70)